filegag.com 2013-06-03

# Filegag.com Your Super file Host

### Privacy Policy 

#### Application and Scope

Stated below is the Privacy Policy (the Privacy Policy) of Filegag.com (FILEGAG, we, our or us). Except where expressly stated otherwise, this Privacy Policy applies only to information collected on FILEGAG Web Site and does not apply to information collected offline or otherwise outside of the FILEGAG Web Site. 

The purpose of this Privacy Policy is to identify the Personal Information we may collect, describe how you can review and make changes to that Personal Information, describe how you can learn about changes to the Privacy Policy, and provide you with a mechanism to opt-out of certain marketing activities. 

Please take a moment to review the terms of this Privacy Policy. Your access and use of any Filegag.com Web Site is conditioned upon your acceptance of the terms stated herein. If you do not agree with one or more of the terms stated in this Privacy Policy, then refrain from using Filegag.com Web Site. From time to time, this Privacy Policy may change. You are responsible for periodically reviewing the latest Privacy Policy to remain knowledgeable of the terms that govern our collection and disclosure of information. 

We also encourage you to review our Terms of Use, posted at Terms Of Use, which govern your use of the FILEGAG Web Site. 

Please note that FILEGAG reserves the right to modify, limit, add or delete, without notice, any of the services discussed in this Privacy Policy. 

#### Information We Can Collect From You

We automatically collect information about your Internet connection, including but not limited to: 

  * The name of the Internet domain you used to access the Internet 
  * The IP address of the web site from which you linked directly to our Site 
  * The content you submit 
  * The date and time you accessed our Site 
  * The pages you visited 

This information ("Non-Personal Information") does not identify you personally. We use this Non-Personal Information to monitor the effectiveness of the Site, to identify areas of interest and to consider potential improvements to the Site. 

We request that you provide certain personally identifiable information ("Personal Information") when you register to participate in services of our Website. We request that you provide name, mailing address, telephone numbers, e-mail address, and payment information such as credit card. We also require you to submit a user name and password of your choice for future access to your information. Your user name and password is to remain confidential and you should not share this information with anyone. 

How We May Use the Information We Collect 

#### Use for Marketing Purposes.

We may use your Personal Information and Non-Personal Information (collectively, Your Information) for our own marketing purposes, including notifying you of special promotions, offers and events via postal mail, e-mail, telephone, text messaging, and other means. If you do not want us to use your Personal Information for marketing purposes, you may opt-out of such uses by notifying us as prescribed below. 

#### Use for Non-Marketing Purposes. 

We may use Your Information for purposes unrelated to marketing, including: 

  * responding to your inquiries, complaints and other communications; 
  * processing and fulfilling orders for and/or purchases of FILEGAG services; 
  * contacting you for confirmation or customer service after you order purchases from FILEGAG Web Site or after you sign up for or participate in certain FILEGAG Web Site services; 
  * for statistical or demographic analysis; 
  * to help improve FILEGAG Web Site and services; 
  * to customize your experience at FILEGAG Web Site; and 
  * for any legal purpose. 

Opting-out of the use of Your Information for marketing purposes will not prevent Your Information from being used for the non-marketing purposes specified above. 

In the event that we engage in joint marketing efforts with third party companies, we may share Your Information with other companies in order to effectuate such marketing efforts. If you do not want us to share Your Information with other companies for marketing purposes you may opt-out of such sharing by notifying us as prescribed below. 

####  Information Disclosed to Affiliates. 

Your Information will be shared for any purpose among FILEGAG departments, subsidiaries and affiliates, such purposes include, without limitation: permitting FILEGAG to validate your identity; completing purchase transactions; or other legitimate non-marketing business needs. 

####  Cookies and Web Beacons

FILEGAG Web Site may utilize a website technology known as cookies primarily to enhance your online experience. A cookie is a small text file that contains information sent by a web site that is saved on your hard drive by your computer�s browser. Cookies can either be permanent (i.e., they remain on your computer until you delete them) or temporary (i.e., they last only until you close your browser). Cookies store information that a website may need to personalize your experience and to gather web site statistical data, such as which web pages you visit, what material you download, your Internet provider�s domain name and country, and the addresses of web sites you visited immediately before and after visiting a particular web site. FILEGAG Web Site use cookies to collect and store your preferences for viewing the FILEGAG Web Site, such as whether you disable a particular function, so that you will not have to disable the same function on following visits. The cookie information may also be used to detect and resolve web site problems and to assist with customer support concerns. 

In addition, FILEGAG Web Site utilizes cookies to provide a unique identifier to your computer. This helps us to generate statistics regarding usage of FILEGAG Web Site, such as the percentage of repeat visitors. In situations where FILEGAG has obtained Personal Information, the unique identifiers may be matched with such Personal Information. In addition, when you submit information to any FILEGAG Web Site the information may be stored in a cookie on our computer and in files generated by third party vendors that assist in the processing and fulfillment of any services offered by FILEGAG Web Site. 

We may also use "web beacons" (also referred to as single-pixel gifs, tracking bugs, tracking pixels, pixel tags, or clear gifs) that monitor your use of our site. Web beacons (or web bugs) are small strings of code that provide a method for delivering a graphic image on a web page for the purpose of transferring data, such as the IP (Internet Protocol) address of the computer that downloaded the page on which the web beacon appears, the URL (Uniform Resource Locator) of the page on which the web beacon appears, the time the page containing the web beacon was viewed, the types of browser that fetched the web beacon and the identification number of any cookie on the computer previously placed by that server. When corresponding with you via HTML capable e-mail, web beacons let us know whether you received and opened our e-mail. 

By accepting this Privacy Policy, you specifically agree to our use of cookies and web beacons as described herein. You may adjust your browser to reject cookies from us or from any other web site. Additionally, by setting your web browser to display HTML e-mails as text only, you may be able to prevent the use of some web beacons. Please consult the "Help" section of your browser for more information. However, certain areas of FILEGAG Web Site can only be accessed in conjunction with cookies or similar devices and you should be aware that disabling cookies or similar devices might prevent you from accessing some of our content. 

#### Security of Information

While FILEGAG strives to secure your Personal Information, even reasonable security measures do not guarantee the security of any information you transmit via the internet, including information submitted to FILEGAG Web Site. FILEGAG cannot guarantee that information it seeks to protect will be protected under all circumstances, including those beyond its reasonable control. By accessing FILEGAG Web Site, you agree that you transmit information to FILEGAG via the FILEGAG Web Site at your own risk. 

#### How You Can Access and/or Correct Your Information. 

If you wish to opt out of receiving solicitations from us or wish to correct Your Information, email us at  and inform us of your preferences

#### To Users Outside of the United States

This website is maintained on servers located within the territorial borders of the United States and subject to its laws, regulations and court precedent. Any of Your Information collected by us in connection with the FILEGAG Web Site shall be subject to the privacy and disclosure laws of the United States. 

#### Children

The Children�s Online Policy Protection Act (COPPA) protects the online privacy of children under the age of 13 years. FILEGAG does not knowingly collect any information from children under the age of thirteen (13), unless or except as permitted by law. Any person who provides Personal information to FILEGAG Web Site represents to us that they are 13 years of age or older. If FILEGAG learns that Personal information collected from user under 13 years of age then FILEGAG will take appropriate steps to delete such information. If you are parent or legal guardian of a child who has become a FILEGAG member, Please contact FILEGAG at  to have that child�s account terminated and information deleted. 

#### Changes to this Privacy Policy

We reserve the right to change, modify or amend this Privacy Policy at any time without notice. When we change, modify and/or amend this Privacy Policy, the revised Privacy Policy will be posted on FILEGAG Web Site. Any revised Privacy Policy will only apply prospectively to Information (Personal or General) collected or modified after the effective date of the revised policy. You are responsible for periodically reviewing the latest Privacy Policy as posted on FILEGAG Web Site. Your continued use of FILEGAG Web Site manifests your assent to any changes made to this Privacy Policy and/or the corresponding Terms of Use. 

#### Contact Information. 

If you have further questions, comments or concerns, please contact us: By emailing us at
